That yesterday Reddy Mart will deliver the leaf till September and
tweet the expenses. The share was
in constant update and it was made at 491 on
Karate September. From there the share turned a little
golden. He has an office meeting. So look at
this level, I believe that there is
a support here at this level. But
if this level is a little then it
can return to 5005. If from here the passbook will
generate its 4.5, like this
rebellion you have done for the world, you can
see this less, you should keep in
mind that the other face is covered.
So this is like this friends, I have
kept spitting and licking like this. When will Tiger discuss on 27th September, then
see, such a room and share will
not eat. I had made the pics of grease on 22nd September.
From there the share
turned a little golden and is a little down.
Look at the crossing at 674 before that and the share is on an
upward trend. So my belief is that friends,
see here if this level will
work as a support with a little education and it will
increase a little. If a
cross is found here then it will go to school at that time.
Subscribe now.